[Music]
Prudential has been in the carom manaro
potential for almost 20 years
well I work in both offices in my tie a
spoon of Prudential so we do spend quite
some time traveling back and forth and
as a result we waste some time when we
see the news about moving to the Newman
our potential we were really very
excited the new working environment will
definitely pramana Java routine
conditions for all employees and one of
the unique feature is the different
themes for different law and we go to be
a part of the new financial district
Malaysia
huija unity is a huge project where we
are bringing for business units into one
building troppa troppa activity and
leprechauns belong Bob indicating animal
let me activity activity near Lancome a
second how Simone package ambassador to
India second diminish why can't you ever
be there but in the colonial memory then
go practice can break the immersion
[Music]
they then began a journey for us to
prepare for the
[Music]
moving here has been a really
interesting experience itself from
packing and moving from our former
premises to adjusting to a brand new
environment my very first time coming to
this office when I walked into the
building I was quite overwhelmed because
of how new and modern the building is so
it's a huge shift from the old building
[Music]
moving to our new premises has allowed
us for greater collaboration all of our
business units credential assurance
Malaysia Berhad credential BSN hakufu is
bring investments and prudential
services asia are within the same
building now before we move my
department was based at our PT office we
must be communicated with our colleagues
base in his view via calls or emails now
that we are in the same building being
able to meet people who are only spoken
with over the phone or with a true
emails has made a world of difference a
new concept that we have here is
activity-based working the whole
constellation we can work anywhere
throughout the floor or throughout the
whole building as well
a lot of thoughts have gone into
designing our new building for more
privacy and a space to do individual
focused work we have focused watts and
flex offices they are also height
adjustable desks wave inward standing or
sitting
[Music]
the urban landscape design teaches
modern and contemporary elements such as
feet our playground team and even a
library to represent our diversity in
arts and house whole thing played on
tradition and heritage and our
preservation areas featured design
elements that incorporate way and Khalid
strong key and traditional games just to
name a few
[Music]
irony in up above fibula
that's our bar as a number affinity
lying now that we have moved into the
new office you know we are very excited
to actually bring you know credential
and year the 14 to greater heights this
is a very exciting journey I can bid for
what's in store for us
may our dreams and ideas together with
courage and conviction continue to
propel us to better serve our customers
and to generate great success of
potential 2019 and beyond
[Music]
you